<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Zhifu</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="biography_text">
        My name is Zhifu Chen, and I\'m a student eager to make the most out of my educational journey.
        With a strong passion for learning and a commitment to personal growth, I strive to excel
        academically while also fostering a sense of curiosity about the world around me.
        In class, you\'ll find me actively engaging in discussions, always ready to share insights
        and learn from my peers. Beyond the classroom, I have a variety of interests that include
        keeping up with the latest technological advancements and delving into books that expand
        my knowledge and imagination.I also value teamwork and believe that working together towards
        a common goal can lead to innovative solutions and enriching experiences. Whether it\'s collaborating
        on a project or simply enjoying downtime with friends, I cherish the moments spent building meaningful
        connections.Looking ahead, I am excited about the opportunities that await and am prepared to
        embrace challenges with enthusiasm and determination. I look forward to contributing
        positively to the community and making lasting friendships along the way.
    </string>
    <string name="hobbies">Hobbies</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="biography">Biography</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="hobbies_text">I love to read, take photographs, and cycle!</string>
    <string name="contact_text">My email is zhifuchen@fake.edu</string>
    <string name="going_to_contact">Going to Contact…</string>
    <string name="email_zhifuchen_fake_edu">Email: zhifuchen@fake.edu</string>
</resources>